Episode 99
What's up?
What are you looking at?
You seem quite serious.
Hey, do you have something on your mind recently?
No, I don't.
It's you who has something on your mind.
I'd like to book a room.
Okay.
Mrs. Bradley, I have
already processed it for you.
It's the room you usually stay in at the hotel.
Mrs. Bradley?
Oh, I accidentally used Niko's card.
Thank you.
Oh.
Hey, hey, hey.
Noemi,
why didn't you reply to my messages?
Huh?
Didn't have anything on your mind? You're wasted
now.
Let me take you home.
Well, I'll take you to the hotel,
the one you usually stay in.
Who is it?
Niko,
what are you doing?
You,
Noemi,
why didn't you reply to my messages?
You already finds a new love,
so why should I reply to your messages?
When did I have a new love?
Huh?
Noemi,
I miss you so much.